[{"product_id":1,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Dragonite","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1941.4,"dues":0,"product_sku":"PKM001001","img_front":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp","discount":9.3,"stock":2,"create_time":"2023-12-18T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":2,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Pidgeotto","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1857.36,"dues":0,"product_sku":"PKM001002","img_front":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp","discount":11.78,"stock":5,"create_time":"2023-10-15T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":3,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Dragonite","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1775.37,"dues":7,"product_sku":"PKM001003","img_front":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp","discount":0.55,"stock":3,"create_time":"2023-11-30T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":4,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Harry","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1719.88,"dues":4,"product_sku":"HPT001004","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp","discount":10.28,"stock":2,"create_time":"2023-12-23T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":5,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Snape Patronus","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1985.16,"dues":6,"product_sku":"HPT001005","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp","discount":12.62,"stock":0,"create_time":"2023-11-08T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":6,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luke","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1925.38,"dues":0,"product_sku":"STW001006","img_front":"/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp","discount":16.98,"stock":0,"create_time":"2023-12-10T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":7,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Hermione","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1892.8,"dues":3,"product_sku":"HPT001007","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp","discount":12.35,"stock":2,"create_time":"2023-11-01T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":8,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luke","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1870.4,"dues":12,"product_sku":"STW001008","img_front":"/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp","discount":15.79,"stock":4,"create_time":"2023-11-06T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":9,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Baby Yoda","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":2068.23,"dues":9,"product_sku":"STW001009","img_front":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp","discount":7.37,"stock":2,"create_time":"2023-11-02T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":10,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Pikachu","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1860.32,"dues":4,"product_sku":"PKM001010","img_front":"/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp","discount":4.95,"stock":4,"create_time":"2023-11-18T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":11,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luna","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1807.66,"dues":7,"product_sku":"HPT001011","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp","discount":10.54,"stock":5,"create_time":"2023-10-26T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":12,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Pidgeotto","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1722.89,"dues":12,"product_sku":"PKM001012","img_front":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp","discount":10.34,"stock":5,"create_time":"2023-10-19T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":13,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Charmander","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1938.57,"dues":2,"product_sku":"PKM001013","img_front":"/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp","discount":7.35,"stock":4,"create_time":"2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":14,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Hermione","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1864.52,"dues":7,"product_sku":"HPT001014","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp","discount":8.09,"stock":3,"create_time":"2023-10-28T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":15,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Trooper","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":2199.18,"dues":7,"product_sku":"STW001015","img_front":"/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp","discount":15.18,"stock":3,"create_time":"2023-10-04T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":16,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Dragonite","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":2037.27,"dues":4,"product_sku":"PKM001016","img_front":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp","discount":17.86,"stock":2,"create_time":"2023-11-05T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":17,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Pikachu","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":2119.98,"dues":12,"product_sku":"PKM001017","img_front":"/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp","discount":0.41,"stock":3,"create_time":"2023-10-03T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":18,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Harry","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1810.01,"dues":11,"product_sku":"HPT001018","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp","discount":19.11,"stock":2,"create_time":"2023-12-30T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":19,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Pidgeotto","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1923.49,"dues":6,"product_sku":"PKM001019","img_front":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp","discount":12.68,"stock":4,"create_time":"2023-11-29T00:00:00.000Z"},{"product_id":20,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Trooper","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1875.44,"dues":7,"product_sku":"STW001020","img_front":"/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp","discount":12.97,"stock":3,"create_time":"2023-11-17T00:00:00.000Z"}]